Guide to the William J. Baumol Papers, 1928-2013 and undated RL.00092
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1946-2012 and undated
  - Articles, Book Chapters, and Other Papers, 1946-2012 and undated; 1
    - Regulation of Public Utility Profits, 1969 (Box 51)
    - Regulation, Litigation, and Misdirection of Entrepreneurship, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Regulatory Impact Analysis Guidance for the Discount Rate, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Relaying the Foundations, 1949 (Box 51)
    - Relazioni Delle Commissioni Giudicatrice dei Premi, 2005 (Box 51)
      Reprint in Italian
    - Report of Econometric Society Meeting, 1950 (Box 51)
    - Reswitching, Social Discount Rate, and Environmental Protections, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Reswitching, social discount rate, and environmentalism: a note, 1996 (Box 37)
    - Retrospective on Baumol, 1992 (Box 13)
      Includes files for Baumol's edits to a retrospective on his work by Bailey and Willig
    - Retrospectives: Say's Law, 1999 (Box 51)
    - Returns in Markets with Psychic Benefits, 2007 (Box 25)
    - Revision Thing, 1992 (Box 52)
      Copy of op-ed for Wall Street Journal
    - Ricardo Effect in the Point-Input-Point-Output Case, 1953 (Box 52)
    - Ricardo Revamped: Trade Rivalries, Large-Scale Industry, and Acquired Learning n the Global Economy, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Rising real performance costs, the cost disease and its consequences, 1997 (Box 37)
    - Rising Real Theatrical Costs, The Cost Disease and its Consequences: A Report on the State of Information on the Cost Problems of the Theatre, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Role of Cost in the Minimum Pricing of Railroad Services, 1962 (Box 52)
    - Routinization for the Innovation Process, 1997 (Box 29)
    - Routinization for the Innovation Process, 1997 (Box 37)
    - Routinization of the Innovation Process Foreign Competition and Income Distribution, 1997 (Box 52)
    - Rules for Beneficial Privatization, 1995 (Box 52)
    - Rules of Thumb and Optimally Imperfect Decisions, 1964 (Box 52)
      Reprint, proofs, and drafts
    - Sales Maximization vs Profit Maximization: Are they Consistent, 1968 (Box 52)
    - Say's at least Eight Laws, or What Say and James Mill May Really Have Meant, 1975-1977 (Box 52)
    - Say's Law, Encyclopedia Entry, 1988 (Box 52)
    - Scale Economies, 1992 (Box 52)
      Includes drafts of various papers on economies of scale
    - Scale Economies and Intertemporal Unsustainability: Toward a Law of Motion of Enterprises, 1979 (Box 52)
    - Scale Economies, Average Cost, and the Profitability of Marginal Cost Pricing, 1976 (Box 52)
    - Schumpeter Revisited, 2000 (Box 25)
    - Schumpeter, Formal Analysis of Innovation, and the Pharmaceuticals, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Schumpeter, Taxes and the Dynamics of Productivity Growth, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Scotland Paper, 2003; 3 folders (Box 23)
    - SEC Requirements for U.S. Listing of Foreign Securities and U.S. Competitiveness, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Sectoral Productivity Growth in the US, 1947-1986, 1988; 17 documents and text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0052)
    - Services as Leaders and the Leader of the Services, 2000 (Box 23)
    - Side Effects of Progress, 1998 (Box 26)
    - Side Effects of Progress, 1998 (Box 52)
    - Sidney Ratner Obituary, undated (Box 36)
    - Simple Derivations of the Parity Theorem, 1996 (Box 24)
    - Sir John Hicks, 1971 (Box 52)
      Includes draft article about the work of John Hicks
    - Sir John Versus the Hicksians, or Theorist Malgre Lui, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Sir John Versus the Hicksians, or Theorist Malgre Lui, 1990 (Box 52)
    - Sir William Arthur Lewis, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Small Firms: Why Market-Driven Innovation Can't Get Along Without Them, 2005 (Box 38)
    - Small Firms: Why Market-Driven Innovation Can't Get Along Without Them, 2005; 2 folders (Box 52)
      Reprint and presentation
    - Smith Versus Marx on Business Morality and the Social Interest, 1978 (Box 52)
    - Social Policy: Pricing devices to aid the invisible hand, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Social Wants and Dismal Science: The Curious Case of the Climbing Costs of Health and Teaching, 1993; 4 folders (Box 29)
      Proofs, copy, and drafts
    - Social Wants and the Dismal Science, 1992-1993; 3 folders (Box 52)
    - Socially Desirable Size of Copyright Fees, 2004 (Box 52)
    - Socially Desirable Size of Copyrights fees, 2004 (Box 37)
    - Solution of Simultaneous Linear Difference Equation Systems, 1954 (Box 52)
    - Some Principles for the Operation of Public Enterprise, 1981 (Box 52)
    - Some Significant Slips in Schumpeter's Scenario, 2010 (Box 52)
    - Some subtle pricing issues in railroad regulation, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Sources of Postwar Growth of Information Activity in the US, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Spatial Equilibrium with Supply Points Separated from Markets and with Supplies Predetermined, 1952 (Box 52)
    - Speculation, Profitability, and Stability, 1957-1958; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Speed of Technology Transmission and the Market Mechanism, 1990; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - State of Humanity, 1995 (Box 36)
    - Statement of Clarification, 1963 (Box 52)
    - Stimulating Growth Amid Recession: Entrepreneurship, Innovation, and the Keynesian Revolution, Undated (Box 25)
    - Stock Market and Economic Efficiency, 1965 (Box 52)
    - Stock Options Report, 2003 (Box 52)
    - Stocks, Flows, and Monetary Theory, 1962 (Box 52)
    - Straddles, 1981 (Box 52)
    - Subsidies to New Energy Sources: Do they Add to Energy Stocks, 1981 (Box 52)
    - Superfairness and Applied Microtheory, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Superfairness theory and rationing policy, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Swing Industries and Productivity Conflict in International Development, 2000 (Box 38)
    - Symposium on the Public Benefits of the Arts and Humanities, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Technical Progress and Sharply Lightened Time 'between jobs', 2000 (Box 23)
    - Technological Change and the New Urban Equilibrium, 1981 (Box 53)
    - Technological Imperatives, Productivity, and Insurance Costs, 1990-1991 (Box 53)
    - Technology Consortia in Complementary Innovations, Dissemination Speed, and the Market, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Technology Consortia in Complementary Innovations, Dissemination Speed, and the Market, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Technology Dissemination and Adaptation, 2003 (Box 37)
    - Technology Transfer and Acquisition, 2000 (Box 26)
    - Telecommunications and Computers: Social Costs of Artificial Separation, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
    - Textbook Economics: Comment on Johansson, 2006 (Box 53)
    - Theory of Equity in Pricing for Resource Conservation, 1980 (Box 53)
    - Theory of the Expansion of the Firm, 1962 (Box 53)
    - Three fables for economists: What's good for your trading partner may not be good for you, 2004 (Box 37)
    - Three fundamental productivity concepts: principles and measurement, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Three Fundamental Productivity Concepts: principles and measurement, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Three Notes on Expectation in Economics, 1949 (Box 53)
    - Ticket Price in the Broadway Theater: Perspective on their Rates of Increase, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Ticket Prices in the Broadway Theatre: Perspective on their Rates of Increase, 1986 (Box 18)
      Working paper co-authored with Hilda Baumol and Edward Wolff
    - Topology of 2nd-order linear difference equations, 1958; 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Toward a Newer Economics: The Future Lies Ahead, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Toward a newer economics: the future lies ahead!, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
    - Toward a Theory of Public Enterprise, 1984; 2 folders (Box 53)
      Reprint, working paper, and drafts
    - Toward Analysis of Capitalism's Unparalleled Growth: Sources and Mechanism, 2004 (Box 53)
    - Toward Analysis of Entrepreneurship, 1982 (Box 53)
    - Toward Analysis of Nonlinear Difference Equations of Higher Order, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Toward Effective Education of Innovative Entrepreneurs in Small Business, 2001 (Box 29)
      Proofs and draft
    - Toward enhancement of the contribution of theory to environmental policy, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Toward enhancement of the contribution of theory to environmental policy, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Toward Operational Models of Entrepreneurship, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Toward Operational Models of Entrepreneurship, 1983 (Box 26)
    - Toward Regional Deregulation in Telecommunications, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Toward the Theory of Public Enterprise, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Towards Microeconomics of Innovation: Growth Engine Hallmark of Market Economies, 2002 (Box 53)
    - Transactions Demand for Cash, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Transactions Demand for Cash: An Inventory Theoretic Approach, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Transcript Interview: Suggested Q, Undated (Box 23)
    - Transformation of Values: What Marx 'Really' Meant (An Interpretation), 1974 (Box 29)
    - Transformation of Values: What Marx "Really" Meant, 1974 (Box 53)
    - Transportation and the City, 1970 (Box 53)
    - Turning a Blind Eye to Issues of Bias Economics, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Turning a blind eye to issues of bias in economics, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Twisting Motion in Abstract Sculptural Forms, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Two-sided cost disease and its frightening consequences, 2010 (Box 53)
    - U.S. Competitiveness and the Productivity Gap, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Unbalanced Growth and 20th Century Productivity Performance in the U.S., 1989 (Box 53)
    - Unbalanced Growth Revisited, 1985 (Box 26)
    - Unbalanced Growth Revisited, 1984 (Box 29)
    - Unbalanced Growth Revisited, 1984 (Box 53)
    - Unbalanced Growth, Composition Effects, and the Productivity Slowdown, 1983 (Box 4)
    - Unmatched Economic Development of the Past two centuries, 2006 (Box 26)
    - Unnatural Value: Or Art Investment as Floating Crap Game, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Unnatural Value: Or Art Investment as Floating Crap Game, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Unpredictability, Pseudorandomness and Military-Civilian Budget Interactions, 1986 (Box 53)
    - Unpredictability, Pseudorandomness and Military-Civilian Budget Interactions, 1983; 9 unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0119)
    - Unprofitable Energy is Squandered Energy, 1980 (Box 26)
    - Unprofitable Energy is Squandered Energy, 1980; 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Unprofitable Energy Sources as Energy Squandered, 1978-1981 (Box 53)
    - Urban Services: Interactions of Public and Private Decisions, 1962; 2 folders (Box 53)
    - US Competitiveness and the Productivity Gap, 1984 (Box 5)
    - US Productivity Growth: History as Antidote for both Hysteria and Complacency, 1985; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - US Productivity Growth: History as Antidote for Both Hysteria and Complacency, 1983-1987; 16 document files (Lotus 1-2-3- format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0100)
    - Use of Antitrust to Subvert Competition, 1984; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Use of Antitrust to Subvert Competition, 1984; 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Use of Standards and Prices for Protection of the Environment, 1971 (Box 53)
    - Valuation of Convertible Securities, 1966 (Box 53)
    - Variables Affecting Success in Economic Education: Preliminary Findings from a new data base, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Variety in Retailing, 1956 (Box 53)
      Reprint and copy
    - Various Papers, 1968-1979; 2 folders (Box 53)
      Includes reprints, copies, and drafts of various papers by Baumol
    - Various Papers, 1976-1984; undated; 12 folders (Box 54)
    - Various Papers, undated (Box 55)
    - Venice Talk: Hope for the Environment: Free Enterprise and other economic regimes, 1998 (Box 38)
    - Viner, Jacob, 1979 (Box 29)
      Copy of entry in the International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences
    - Von-Neumann-Morgenstern Utility Index, 1951 (Box 55)
    - Von-Neumann-Morgenstern Utility Index, 1951 (Box 84)
    - Wages, Virtue and Value: What Marx Really Said, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Wash. Post Moynihan - Health Care, 1993 (Box 55)
      Copy of article published in the Washington Post
    - Wassily Leontief: In Appreciation, 2003 (Box 55)
    - We can have it all: Why health care will still be affordable, 2012 (Box 25)
    - We can have it all: Why health care will still be affordable, 2012 (Box 55)
    - Weak Invisible Hand Theorems on the Sustainability of Multi-Product Natural Monopoly, 1977; undated; 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Welfare Economics and the Theory of the State, 1952 (Box 55)
    - What Can Economic Theory Contribute to Managerial Economics, 1961 (Box 55)
    - What Marshall Didn't Know: On the Twentieth Century's Contributions to Economics, 2000 (Box 55)
    - What Price Economic Growth, 1961 (Box 55)
    - What's Different about European Economics, 1995 (Box 55)
    - Wheatsheet Prefaces, 1984 (Box 55)
    - When is Inter-firm Coordination Benefician? The Case of Innovation, 1999 (Box 38)
    - When is Inter-firm Coordination Benefician? The Case of Innovation, 2001 (Box 55)
    - Will Deregulation Produce a Competitive Market for Long Haul Services?, 1987 (Box 4)
    - William Arthur Lewis: Memorial Note, 1991 (Box 6)
    - William Baumol on Productivity, Competition, and Marmalade, 1985 (Box 55)
    - William J. Baumol: An Entrepreneurial Economist on the Economics of Entrepreneurship, 2003 (Box 37)
    - Williamson's The Economic Institutions of Capitalism, 1986 (Box 55)
    - Wine Pricing, Capital Theory, and Practice, 1960 (Box 55)
    - Writings on contestable markets and chaos, 1983-1988; 58 document and text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0051)
    - Writings on information and industry structure, 1983-1986; 12 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0113)
    - Writings on productivity growth, 1990; 8 text and unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0030)
    - Writings on quality and productivity changes, 1989; 13 document, text, and unidentified formats; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0031)
    - Yes, the US is not doing badly, but the Laffer Curve Remains no laughing matter, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Yet Another Note on the Harrod-Domar Model, 1952 (Box 55)
  - Books, 1951-2010 and undated; 2
    Contains copies, draft materials, and related correspondence for books authored and edited by Baumol.
    - Adapting Antitrust to the New Economy, 2002-2006; 6 folders (Box 26)
    - Adapting Antitrust to the New Economy, 2001; 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Adventures in Chinese Grocery Shopping, undated; 4 folders (Box 55)
      Includes drafts of a cookbook co-authored with Hilda Baumol, Paula Chow, and Gregory Chow
    - Antitrust volume, 2002-2003; 3 folders (Box 14)
      Includes draft materials and correspondence related to volume on antitrust policy
    - Arts Book (Baumol Compendium), 1995 (Box 23)
      Includes material for book on Baumol's art
    - Baumol and Blinder Principles book, 1992-2007; 29 folders (Box 35)
      Includes draft materials and related files for the 10th edition of textbook co-authored with Alan Blinder
    - Baumol-Bowen Performing Arts Book, 2007 (Box 23)
      Includes correspondence related to book publication with MIT Press
    - Baumol/Gomory Book, 1997; 8 folders (Box 37)
      Includes draft chapters for Global Trade and Conflicting National Interests
    - Becker/Baumol Book, 2001 (Box 36)
    - Book Proposal: Adventures in Chinese Grocery Shopping, undated (Box 23)
      Includes draft book proposal co-authored by Paula Chow and Hilda Baumol
    - Business Behavior, Value, and Growth, 1959; 1967; 4 folders (Box 56)
      Harcourt, Brace, and World. Includes hardcover and paperback versions, drafts, and related correspondence
    - Contestable Markets and the Theory of Industry Structure, 1982 (Box 56)
      Harcourt, Brace, and Jovanovich
    - Contestable Markets and the Theory of Industry Structure, 1987-1990 (Box 23)
      Includes materials related to second edition of the book
    - Cost Disease, 2010 (Box 56)
      Includes correspondence
    - Draft Chapter on Monopoly Power, 2002 (Box 24)
      Includes draft book chapter
    - Draft Chapters on "New Economy" and Contestability, 2002 (Box 24)
      Includes draft book chapters
    - Economic Dynamics, 1951; 2 folders (Box 56)
      Macmillan. Includes drafts, notes, and related correspondence
    - Economic Theory and Operations Analysis, 1979-1990; 3 folders (Box 56)
      Includes draft material, notes, and related correspondence
    - Economic Theory and Operations Analysis, 1968 (Box 56)
      Hungarian translation
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1993; 23 folders (Box 2)
      Includes materials for 6th edition of textbook with Alan Blinder
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1992 (Box 13)
      Includes files for 6th edition of textbook with Alan Blinder
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1984 (Box 14)
      Includes materials for 3rd edition of textbook with Alan Blinder
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1979-2010; 7 folders (Box 56)
      Includes files and materials for various editions of textbook co-authored with Alan Blinder
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1991-2007; 16 folders (Box 57)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1999 (Box 23)
      Includes materials for 9th edition of textbook with Alan Blinder
    - Economics: Principles and Policy - Productivity Problems, 1984-1987 (Box 5)
      Includes drafts from 3rd edition of textbook by Baumol and Blinder
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1990; 22 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0087)
      Includes files for textbook co-authored with Alan Blinder.
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1987-1988; 28 document and unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0044)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1988; 3 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0045)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1988; 31 document files (Lotus 1-2-3- format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0047)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1987-1988; 35 document and text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0048)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1987; 5 unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0122)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1987; 2 unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0123)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 2006; 43 document (Word format); approximately 4 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-OP-0001)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1980-1987; 10 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0016)
    - Economics: Principles and Policy, 1980-1987; 13 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0018)
    - Education for Innovation: Entrepreneurial Breakthroughs vs. Corporate Incremental Improvements, 2004; 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Electricity monograph, 1994; 2 folders (Box 38)
      Includes draft monograph for electric company policies on interacting with vendors, as well as related materials
    - Entrepreneurship History Book, 2005; 3 folders (Box 37)
      Includes draft materials for book on the history of entrepreneurship
    - Entrepreneurship Theory Book, 2006 (Box 14)
    - Entrepreneurship Theory Chapters, 2006; 13 document files (Word format); approximately 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-OP-0005)
      Includes draft chapters for book on entrepeneurship.
    - Entrepreneurship, Innovation, and the Growth Mechanism of the Free-Enterprise Economies, 2007; 2 folders (Box 57)
      Includes drafts of volume edited with Eytan Sheshinski and Robert Strom
    - Entrepreneurship, Innovation, and the Growth Mechanism of the Free-Enterprise Economies, 2007; 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Fairness Book, 1963 (Box 58)
      Includes draft chapters
    - Feedback and Productivity, 1993 (Box 34)
      Draft materials
    - Files for an unidentified book project, 1994; 3 document files (WordPerfect format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL3-0002)
      Title of project is unclear from files.
    - Files for an unidentified book project, 1994; 1 document file (WordPerfect format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL3-0003)
      Title of project is unclear from the files.
    - Free-Market Innovation Machine, 2002; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Free-Market Innovation Machine, 2000-2002; 8 folders (Box 29)
      Includes draft chapters, notes, and related correspondence
    - Free-Market Innovation Machine, 2001 (Box 23)
    - Global Trade and Conflicting National Interests, 2000 (Box 14)
      Include draft materials for book co-authored with Ralph Gomory
    - Global Trade and Conflicting National Interests, 1999-2001; undated; 9 folders (Box 58)
      Includes drafts, notes, and correspondence for manuscript co-authored with Ralph Gomory
    - Global Trade Theory: Productivity Growth Differentials and Scale Economies, 2004-2007; 3 folders (Box 34)
    - Good Capitalism, Bad Capitalism, 2007 (Box 58)
      Includes drafts
    - Growth, Industrial Organization, and Economic Generalities, 1992-2004; 4 folders (Box 58)
      Includes drafts and research materials
    - History of Economic Thought Book Project, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Inflation and the Performing Arts, 1984; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Inflation and the Performing Arts, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
      Includes publishing agreement and related correspondence
    - Invention of Enterprise, 2005-2007; 3 folders (Box 14)
      Includes draft materials and correspondence for volume on the history of entrepreneurship edited with David Landes and Joel Mokyr
    - Kauffman and NYU book - The Invention of Enterprise, 2008; 7 document files (PDF format); approximately 7 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-OP-0006)
      Includes draft of book on history of entrepreneurship.
    - Lionel Robbins History of Economic Thought Lectures Book, undated (Box 36)
      Includes draft material for Robbins's book of lectures on the history of economic thought and Baumol's foreword for the book
    - Microtheory: Applications and Origins, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Performing Arts: Economic Dilemma, 1981 (Box 18)
      Includes materials related to research and publication
    - Performing Arts: Economic Dilemma, 2nd edition, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
    - Principles of Public Interest Regulation, undated (Box 29)
      Includes outline and draft materials
    - Principles of Public-Interest Regulation, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
      Includes draft materials for book with Willig
    - Productivity and American Leadership: The Long View, 1986-1990; 27 folders (Box 7)
      Includes draft materials, original artwork, research materials, and related correspondence for book co-authored with Sue Ann Batey Blackman and Edward Wolff
    - Productivity Book, 1986 (Box 59)
      Includes draft material
    - Productivity Book, 1987; 8 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0056)
    - Productivity Book, 1987; 5 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0063)
    - Productivity Book, 1987; 1 text file; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0064)
    - Productivity Book, 1988; 6 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0065)